Guide to the New York University Archives Photographic Slides Collection MC.339
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Photographic Slides Collection
1900-2002
New York University Archives
New York University. School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions
MC.339
42 Linear Feet in 1 card box, 1 flat box, 22 half manuscript boxes, and 71 manuscript boxes
The New York University Archives Photographic Slides Collection was created by the University Archives to group together slides documenting New York University activities, schools and departments, staff, students, buildings, and classrooms. Materials in the collection date from 1900 to 2002, with the bulk of the slides dating from the 1970s to 2002.
Scope and Contents
The New York University Archives Photographic Slides Collection consists of binders of slides documenting various University activities, schools and departments, staff, students, buildings, and classrooms. Materials in the collection document the School of Education, Health, Nursing and Arts Professions; the College of Arts and Sciences; Tisch School of the Arts; Stern School of Business; and the School of Professional Studies. Materials in the collection date from 1900 to 2002, with the bulk of the slides dating from the 1970s to 2002.
Historical Note
The New York University Archives Photographic Slides Collection was created by the University Archives to group together slides documenting New York University activities, schools and departments, staff, students, buildings, and classrooms. Slides were transferred from university schools and departments, including School of Education, Health, Nursing and Arts Professions.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by topic.
Conditions Governing Access
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact the Archives with specific questions regarding access to such records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Some materials in this collection were transferred from various New York University departments in 1990 and 1992. No information was recorded about the acquisition of the other materials in this collection. The accession numbers associated with these transfers include 90.023 and 92.021.
Slides (Photography); College students -- New York (N.Y.); College buildings.
- Binder 1: Administration, 1983 (Box 1)
- Binder 2: Services, 1983-1988 (Box 2)
- Binder 3: Admissions, 1986-1988 (Box 3)
- Binder 4: Orientation I, 1985-1987 (Box 4)
- Binder 5: Orientation II, 1985-1987 (Box 5)
- Binder 6: Faculty and Alumni, 1983-1988 (Box 6)
- Binder 7: NYU Schools, CAS I, 1983-1989 (Box 7)
- Binder 8: NYU Schools II, CAS II, 1959-1988 (Box 8)
- Binder 9: NYU Schools III, CAS III, 1972-1985 (Box 9)
- Binder 10: NYU Schools IV, BPA/Commerce/ GPA, 1964-1989 (Box 10)
- Binder 11: NYU Schools V, Professional I, 1971-1989 (Box 11)
- Binder 12: NYU Schools VI, Professional II, 1983-1987 (Box 12)
- Binder 13: NYU Schools VII, SOA/Tisch I, 1973-1989 (Box 13)
- Binder 14: NYU Schools VIII, SOA/Tisch II, 1980-1994 (Box 14)
- Binder 15: NYU Buildings I, 1964-1997 (Box 15)
- Binder 15A: NYU Buildings I, 1973-1989 (Box 15A)
- Binder 15B: NYU Buildings I, 1973-1999 (Box 15B)
- Binder 15C: NYU Buildings I, 1973-1988 (Box 15C)
- Binder 16: NYU Buildings II, 1972-1992 (Box 16)
- Binder 16A: NYU Buildings II, 1975-2001 (Box 16A)
- Binder 17: NYU Dorms I, 1985-1989 (Box 17)
- Binder 17A: NYU Dorms I, 1983-1989 (Box 17A)
- Binder 18: NYU Dorms Ii, 1985-1988 (Box 18)
- Binder 19: Bobst Library I, 1968-1974 (Box 19)
- Binder 20: Bobst Library II, 1973-1985 (Box 20)
- Binder 21: Student Government and Career Planning, 1982-1989 (Box 21)
- Binder 22: Classroom Scenes, 1979-1988 (Box 22)
- Binder 23: Campus Scenes, 1983-1988 (Box 23)
- Binder 24: Campus Scenes II, 1977-1989 (Box 24)
- Binder 25: Campus Scenes III, 1979-1989 (Box 25)
- Binder 26: Campus Scenes IV, 1986-1989 (Box 26)
- Binder 27: Student Activities I, 1985-1987 (Box 27)
- Binder 27A: Student Activities I, 1980-1987 (Box 27A)
- Binder 28: Student Activities II, 1985-1998 (Box 28)
- Binder 29: NYU Students in New York City, 1986-1990 (Box 29)
- Binder 30: NYU Sports, 1982-1994 (Box 30)
- Binder 31: Special Events I, 1986-1989 (Box 31)
- Binder 32: Special Events II, 1988-1989 (Box 32)
- Binder 33: Special Events III, 1975-1989 (Box 33)
- Binder 34: Special Events IV, 1981-1988 (Box 34)
- Binder 35: Special Events V, 1979-1989 (Box 35)
- Binder 36: Special Events VI, 1983-1985 (Box 36)
- Binder 37: Special Events VII, 1987-1989 (Box 37)
- Binder 38: Special Events VIII, 1984-1994 (Box 38)
- Binder 39: Special Events IX, 1984-1994 (Box 39)
- Binder 40: Special Events X, 1987-1990 (Box 40)
- Binder 41: Special Events XI, 1986-1988 (Box 41)
- Binder 42: Special Events XII, 1981-1995 (Box 42)
- Binder 43: Special Events XIII, 1990-1992 (Box 43)
- Binder 44: Special Events XIV, 1984-1995 (Box 44)
- Binder 45: Special Events XV, 1986-1997 (Box 45)
- Binder 46: University Heights, 1943-1970 (Box 46)
- Binder 47: Slide Presentations, 1979-1984 (Box 47)
- Binder 47A: Slide Presentations, 1987-1995 (Box 47A)
- Slide Presentations, 1986-1996 (Box 47B)
- Binder 48: Hester Presentation, 1970-1985 (Box 48)
- Binder 49: Non-NYU Subjects, 1963-1986 (Box 49)
- Binder 49A: Non-NYU Subjects, 1972-1992 (Box 49A)
- Binder 50: Trustees, 1999 (Box 50)
- Binder 51: Trustees, 1999 (Box 50)
- Binder 52: Special Events, 2000 (Box 52)
- Binder 53: Special Events, 2001 (Box 52)
- Binder 54: Special Events, 2002 (Box 52)
- Binder 55: University Senate, 1996-2000 (Box 55)
- Binder 56: University Senate, 1900 (Box 56)
- Binder 57: NYU Icons, 1969-1991 (Box 57)
- Commencement Binder 1, 1959-1975 (Box 58)
- Commencement Binder 2, 1976-1978 (Box 58A)
- Commencement Binder 3, 1979 (Box 58)
- Commencement Binder 4, 1980 (Box 59)
- Commencement Binder 5, 1981 (Box 60)
- Commencement Binder 6, 1982 (Box 61)
- Commencement Binder 7, 1983 (Box 62)
- Commencement Binder 8, 1984 (Box 63)
- Commencement Binder 9, 1985 (Box 64)
- Commencement Binder 10, 1986 (Box 65)
- Commencement Binder 11, 1987 (Box 66)
- Commencement Binder 12, 1988 (Box 67)
- Commencement, 1989 (Box 68)
- Commencement Binder 15, 1986-1993 (Box 69)
- Commencement Binder 16, 1994 (Box 70)
- Commencement Binder 17, 1900 (Box 70)
- Commencement Binder18, 1995 (Box 71)
- Commencement Binder 19, 1996 (Box 72)
- Commencement Binder 20, 1997 (Box 73)
- Commencement Binder 21, 1997 (Box 73A)
- Commencement Binder 22, 1998 (Box 73A)
- SEHNAP Binder 1: Administrtion/Alumni/Faculty, 1966-1983 (Box 74)
- SEHNAP Binder 2, 3: Health and Nursing, 1983-1989 (Box 75)
- SEHNAP Binder 4: Arts/Crafts, 1968-1989 (Box 76)
- SEHNAP Binder 5: Other Programs I, 1978-1989 (Box 77)
- SEHNAP Binder 6: Other Programs II, 1964-1987 (Box 78)
- SEHNAP Binder 7: Slide Presentations, 1977-1981 (Box 79)
- SEHNAP Binder 8: Educational Theater I, 1977-1981 (Box 80)
- SEHNAP Binder 9: Educational Theater II, 1966-1982 (Box 81)
- SEHNAP Binder 10: Educational Theater III, 1968-1987 (Box 82)
- SEHNAP Binder 11: Educational Theater IV, 1973-1983 (Box 83)
- SEHNAP Binder 12: Educational Theater V, 1975-1982 (Box 84)
- SEHNAP Binder 13: Educational Theater VI, 1978-1985 (Box 85)
- SEHNAP Binder 14: Educational Theater VII, 1975-1987 (Box 86)
- Index cards, loose slides (Box 87)